payzippy.com 2016-03-10

# PayZippy Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, wherever the context so requires 'You' shall mean any natural or legal person who avails the services. The term "We", "Us", "Our" shall mean Flipkart Payment Gateway Services Private Limited. The terms, 'FKPG', 'Payzippy' may be used interchangeably in this document as the context may require and the same shall refer to Flipkart Payment Gateway Services Private Limited.

**Note:** Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this Services you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Services.

By mere use of the Services, you expressly consent to our use and appropriate disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy is subject to the 'Terms of Use', which has been separately made available in this Website. 

1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information

When you make financial transactions using Payzippy, we collect and store your personal and payment transaction details which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized transaction experience. This allows us to provide services and features that meet your needs, and to customize our Services to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

1. It is clearly specified and understood by you that all information pertaining to your financial transaction credit card/ debit card and all other financial instruments shall be protected as per below standards.  

a. 128-bit encryption to and from the servers and web browser. All confidential data pertaining Your financial transactions, which are lying with Us are protected by using AES -256 standard encryption method.

b. Once the information is transmitted to our servers for processing, we use encryption in the back end to transmit the request to our payment processor to verify the credit card and place an authorization for the order total.

2. We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us. While you can browse some sections of our Services without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Services or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Services or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

3. We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Services to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie".

4. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Services and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

5.If you transact with us, we collect information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details.

2\. Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information

a. We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

b. In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyse demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Services.

c. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Services. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

d. We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our Services, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. 

3\. Sharing of personal information

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

4\. Links to Other Sites

Our Services may link to other Servicess that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Payzippy.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked Services. 

5\. Security Precautions

Our Services has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

6\. Choice/Opt-Out

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. If you want to remove your contact information from all payzippy.com lists and newsletters, You may please click on the unsubscribe link provided thereunder. 

7\. Your Consent

By using the Services and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Services in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

8\. Grievance Officer

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

Mr. Fareed Jawad  
Flipkart Payment Gateway Services Pvt. Ltd.  
Brigade Manae Court, Second Floor, No.111  
Industrial Layout, Koramangala  
Bangalore 560034  
Email: [grievanceofficer@payzippy.com](mailto:grievanceofficer@payzippy.com)

9\. Questions?

Questions regarding the use of the Services and services should be directed to [care@payzippy.com](mailto:care@payzippy.com)
